여기
Here.
진짜 어이없다
You guys are unbelievable.
니넨 모험을 시뮬레이션 하는 게임은 하는데
You play a game to simulate adventure,
현실 세계에 진짜 모험이 있으면 니넨 겁쟁이가 되지
but when there's real adventure out there in the real world, you just wimp out.
Leonard, 너 그 사람한테 갔을 때 바지 안 입고 집에 온 거 기억 안나?
Leonard, do you not recall the last time we visited this gentleman, we returned home without pants?
기억 나지 - 진심이야?
I do. - Are you sure?
니가 가자고 하는 거 보면 기억 못하는 거 같아서
Because your proposal suggests that you don't.
나 그 사람 안 무서워 - 그래 Leonard가 이런 질문을 제안하는 거 같은데
I'm not afraid of him. - All right. Leonard fairly calls the question:
누가 우리의 게임을 망치고 싶어하고 스테로이드 맞은 페니 전 남친이랑 싸우려고 하고
Who is in favor of abandoning our game and confronting Penny's steroid-infused ex-boyfriend